biblica.com 2018-10-19

# Privacy Policy | Biblica - The International Bible Society

Please [click here](https://www.biblica.com/terms-of-use/) to view the Terms of Use page.

Biblica US, Inc. (“Biblica”) has created this privacy statement to let businesses, consumers, and the general public know how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us.

**Contact Information**

To request a correction or deletion of your personal information, or if you have any questions and general comments about this privacy policy, please contact us at:

E-mail: _[Contact Us Form](https://www.biblica.com/about/contact-us/)_

Phone: Toll-free at 800-497-1121 or 719-488-9200

Surface mailing address: Biblica, 1820 Jet Stream Drive, Colorado Spring, CO 80921

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When visiting our web sites, you may provide us with two types of information, (i) personal information you voluntarily choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and, (ii) web site use information gathered on a collective basis as you and others browse our web site. For analytics and statistics tracking purposes, Biblica collects your IP address automatically when you visit our website (this may appear in our own server logs as well as Google Analytics data). In some cases, your IP address is considered personally identifiable data. Aside from collecting your IP address, we do not collect any other personally identifiable information without your knowledge while you are visiting our website. The type of information we collect directly corresponds with the service you request. For instance, you can offer your thoughts, opinions, prayers, concerns, ideas, personal experiences, questions, and/or suggestions to our articles or materials; or you can request that a resource be sent to you directly. The type of information we collect is only the information necessary to facilitate our response to your specific request such as your name and contact information. If you request to have a resource sent to you, Biblica will collect the information necessary to complete this transaction that may include your contact information, credit card number, and other transaction information. If you offer your thoughts, comments, opinions, concerns, ideas, and/or personal experience testimonies, or request prayer, ask questions, etc., Biblica collects that information and may use the information in one of the ways set forth in the following section titled “Use of Information.”

**What do we consider personal data for citizens of the European Union?**

Biblica operates in compliance of the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) as it pertains to how we handle and define data we collect from citizens of countries within the EU. For people under EU and GDPR jurisdiction, personal data is defined as:

 “any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person”.

**Use of Information**

Biblica retains all rights to use the information provided by you to:

  * Respond to your correspondence, questions, comments, suggestions, thoughts, opinions, prayers, concerns, or ideas to fulfill a resource request.
  * Process your request for resources from our online resource services.
  * Continually update, develop, design, and customize the content of our website to meet the needs, interests, and requests of our audience.
  * Contact you via e-mail to confirm specific resource or information requests, inform you of new products and special offers, or provide information we think may be of particular interest to you (you can opt out of these and other emails from us at any time by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email, or by contacting us via our [Contact Us form](https://www.biblica.com/about/contact-us/)).

**Type of information collected automatically**

Biblica collects the following categories of data that can be classified as personal data in certain instances or jurisdictions:

  * Your IP address (This allows us to know where you are geographically for statistics tracking purposes. It is also logged automatically by our servers for security and troubleshooting purposes.)
  * Your browsing activity on our website (This allows us to make decisions based on the popularity of any given pages or based on how people navigate our website)
  * Whether or not your browsing session is tied to a Facebook account, Google account, or other non-account based online advertising networks that we utilize (We do this through tracking pixels which are automatically loaded when you open our website. These pixels allow us to track your behavior on our website. Depending on your activity, we may choose to target relevant advertising to you on Facebook, Google, or other platforms. You can opt out of our use of pixels to track your behavior by submitting our [contact us form](https://www.biblica.com/about/contact-us/), or contacting our GDPR Owner.)

**Type of information collected only when you specifically give it to us**

Biblica collects the following categories of personal data when you submit it to us:

  * Your name
  * Your mailing and/or billing address
  * Your email address
  * Your phone number
  * Any personal information that you volunteer as a prayer request
  * Any personal information included with your donation when submitting an online donation
  * Any personal information that you volunteer by submitting our contact form, emailing us, including a comment with your donation, messaging us on our social media platforms, or posting a comment in any of our comment areas on articles or any of our social media platforms

**With Whom Do We Share Information**

We may share information about you with third parties in certain circumstances including in the following situations:

Affiliates. We may share all types of information with organizations that we own or control, or that own or control us.

Blogs, Online Postings, and Testimonials. We may share with the public any information that you publish in conjunction with an on-line review, comment, blog, or message board.

Transition. In the event that we, or part, or all, of our assets are acquired, we may share all types of information with the acquiring organization. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,

Law Enforcement. We may report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we reasonably believe to be unlawful, or that we believe may aid a law enforcement investigation. In addition, we reserve the right to release all types of information to law enforcement agencies if we determine, in our sole judgment, that either you have violated our policies, or the release of information about you may protect the rights, property or safety of us or another person.

Legal Processes. We may share all types of information with others as required by, or permitted by, law. This may include sharing information with governmental entities, or third parties in response to subpoenas, court orders, other legal process, or as we believe is necessary to exercise our legal rights, to defend against legal claims that have been brought against us, or to defend against possible legal claims that we determine in our sole discretion might be brought against us.

Service Providers. We share information with people and companies that provide us with services. These services may include, among other things, helping us provide products or services that you request, creating or maintaining our databases, researching or analyzing the people and financial backgrounds of people who use our websites, or processing payment card information.

**How Do We Safeguard Personal Data of EU Citizens With Certain Rights Under GDPR**

When personal data being handled involves an individual who is a citizen of any country within the EU specifically, we take certain steps to ensure your personal data is protected under GDPR. These steps include, but are not limited to:

  * We ensure that your personal data does not get sent to third-party vendors who do not have specific business reasons to possess it. (i.e. We will send your data to companies that help us analyze your data on our behalf for our own business purposes. We will also send your data to third-party companies when we are obligated to do so due to contractual reasons.)
  * When we no longer require your data to fulfill any service for which it was initially retained, we will dispose of the data in line with Biblica’s data retention procedures. As a general rule, personal data is not manually saved for periods longer than necessary, but may exist on certain systems and platforms of ours indefinitely in backups and other forms of automated retention as needed, particularly when there are legal reasons for retention such as for income tax and audit purposes.
  * How long certain kinds of personal data should be kept may also be governed by specific business-sector requirements and agreed practices. Personal data may be held in addition to these periods depending on individual business needs.

**Specific Third-Party Companies and Organizations With Whom We May Share Information**

As generally stated above, we may share your information with many different third-parties. While this is not an exhaustive list, in general, here are some of the third-party companies, organizations, and platforms with which we work.

  * NeonCRM (This company is located within the U.S. and works specifically with U.S.-based organizations to collect donations from donors and allow potential donors to become donors by submitting online forms. To learn more about the safeguards that NeonCRM has in place to protect data within its platform, please visit their website or contact them directly.)
  * PostUp (This company is located within the U.S. and works with companies and organizations worldwide, allowing them send marketing and other emails to lists of opted-in users. When you sign up for our newsletter, daily devotionals, Daily Manna, or other lists we may manage, your name and email address will be stored within PostUp for our exclusive use. We do not sell, lease, or in any way provide your email address to other lists outside of Biblica, and we will not add you to any of our lists that you have not explicitly opted into. To learn more about the safeguards that PostUp has in place to protect data within its platform, please visit their website or contact them directly.)
  * net (This company is located within the U.S. and works with companies and organizations worldwide, processing credit card transactions. When you submit an Online Donation Form, your donation will be processed through Authorize.net. Biblica does not have access to the full credit card numbers for transactions, this information is available only to Authorize.net. To learn more about the safeguards that Authorize.net has in place to protect data within its platform, please visit their website or contact them directly.)

**What are “Cookies” and How Do We Use Information We Collect from Them?**

Our site uses cookies to differentiate you from other customers and to enhance your onsite experience by preventing repeated ads or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our web server’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies. Cookies are considered industry standard. Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. If you choose to alter your browser to refuse cookies, it is possible some areas of our site will not function properly when you view them.

**How to Opt Out of Tracking Pixels and Cookies**

If you do not wish to have tracking pixels or cookies stored on your computer when you visit our website, you can disable or opt out of these practices by following the applicable steps outlined below.

To opt out of tracking pixels and cookies used by specific services we utilize:

  * Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/>
  * Google Ads: <https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en>
  * Google Analytics: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>
  * Taboola: <https://www.taboola.com/cookie-policy> (See item 4)

To clear or block cookies for our website at the browser level:

  * Google Chrome: <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647>
  * Mozilla Firefox: <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/block-websites-storing-site-preferences#w_block-cookies-for-a-single-website>
  * Microsoft Internet Explorer: <https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies>
  * Safari for macOS: <https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411?locale=en_US>

You can also use a Private or Incognito browser window to browse our website without having tracking pixels and cookies saved. Please note, however, that if you are currently logged into Google, Facebook, or other services we use in a separate tab within your private browser, tracking technology may still be used until you close the private browser window.

If you have any specific questions about any tracking pixels or cookies not mentioned here, please contact us at [webmaster@biblica.com](mailto:webmaster@biblica.com).

**Data Retention Period**

Data retention of your personal data may vary depending on where it resides in our various systems and platforms, however, we generally will retain your data as follows:

  * IP addresses and browsing activity within our website is retained in various forms indefinitely.
  * Your donation and financial records with us are retained for at least seven (7) years, as per IRS regulations, and may be retained both digitally and physically (printed).
  * Any information you submit to us manually through any of our contact forms, email addresses, or social media platforms, could be retained indefinitely and may be retained in backups or moved to other platforms of ours in order for us to better serve you or respond to you.
  * Emails that you send us are generally retained for a period of 5 years, but certain emails may continue to exist in various forms or digital backups indefinitely.

**Specific Rights Granted to Citizens of the European Union Subject to GDPR Rights and Jurisdiction:**

If we are in possession of or are processing any of your personal data, you have the following rights:

  * **Right of access** – You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you.
  * **Right of rectification** – You have a right to correct data that we hold about you that is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * **Right to be forgotten** – In certain circumstances you can ask for the data we hold about you to be erased from our records.
  * **Right to restriction of processing** – Where certain conditions apply to have a right to restrict the processing of personally identifiable data.
  * **Right of portability** – You have the right to have the data we hold about you transferred to another organization.
  * **Right to object** – You have the right to object to certain types of processing such as direct marketing.
  * **Right to object to automated processing, including profiling** – You also have the right to be subject to the legal effects of automated processing or profiling.
  * **Right to judicial review** – If Biblica refuses your request under rights of access, we will provide you with a reason as to why. You have the right to complain as outlined in the section titled “Complaints Regarding Personal Data Use” below.

All the above requests will be forwarded on should there be a third party involved in the processing of your personal data. All requests to exercise any individual rights under GDPR are subject to proof of identity as outlined under “Proof of Identity for GDPR Related Requests” below.

**Complaints Regarding Personal Data Use of Citizens Subject to GDPR Jurisdiction**

In the event that you wish to make a complaint about how your personal data is being processed by Biblica (or third parties that we work with to handle your data), or how your complaint has been handled, you have the right to lodge a complaint directly with the supervisory authority and Biblica’s data protection representatives. You can do so by contacting Marius Roetz, who serves as our Data Protection Officer (DPO)/GDPR Owner. Marius Roetz can be contacted at [legal@biblica.com](mailto:legal@biblica.com) or by mailing 1820 Jet Stream Drive, Colorado Springs, CO 80921, or via our [Contact Us form](https://www.biblica.com/about/contact-us/).

**What Personal Information Do You Hold About Me?**

Biblica at your request, can confirm what information we hold about you and how it is processed. All requests for personal information under GDPR are subject to proof of identity as outlined under “Proof of Identity for GDPR Related Requests” below. If we do hold personal data about you, you can request the following information:

  * Identity and the contact details of the person or organization that has determined how and why to process your data. In some cases, this will be a representative in the EU.
  * Contact details of the data protection officer, where applicable.
  * The purpose of the processing as well as the legal basis for processing.
  * If the processing is based on the legitimate interests of Biblica or a third party, information about those interests.
  * The categories of personal data collected, stored, and processed.
  * Recipient(s) or categories of recipients that the data is/will be disclosed to.
  * If we intend to transfer the personal data to a third country or international organization, information about how we ensure this is done securely. The EU has approved sending personal data to some countries because they meet a minimum standard of data protection. In other cases, we will ensure there are specific measures in place to secure your information.
  * How long the data will be stored.
  * Details of your rights to correct, erase, restrict or object to such processing.
  * Information about your right to withdraw consent at any time.
  * How to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority.
  * Whether the provision of personal data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract, as well as whether you are obliged to provide the personal data and the possible consequences of failing to provide such data.
  * The source of personal data if it wasn’t collected directly from you.
  * Any details and information of automated decision making, such as profiling, and any meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and expected consequences of such processing.

**How to Exercise Your GDPR Rights or Request Personal Data Under GDPR**

If you qualify for GDPR rights and are requesting information regarding the personal data we hold on you specifically, or if you wish to exercise any rights granted to you under GDPR, we require you to provide proof of your identity. This requires some work on your part, but also helps us insure that your data is protected from third-parties who may be requesting it on your behalf without your permission. GDPR related requests can be submitted via the following channels:

  * Our [Contact Us form](https://www.biblica.com/about/contact-us/)
  * By sending physical mail to offices at 1820 Jet Stream Drive, Colorado Springs, CO 80921
  * Calling us at toll-free at 800-497-1121 or 719-488-9200
  * By emailing our Data Protection Officer (DPO)/GDPR Owner at [legal@biblica.com](mailto:legal@biblica.com)

To provide proof of your identity, please make a copy of at least one of the following documents: your passport, driver’s license, or birth certificate. Please also attach a copy of a bank or credit card statement or utility bill from within the last three months that clearly shows your current address. If you have changed your name, please provide valid evidence of your legal name change as it pertains to your identity documentation.

If you are unable to provide the above documentation, or if we have reason to believe an unauthorized third party may have compromised your identity and is requesting your information on your behalf, we reserve the right to request that the above evidence be witnessed and notarized by a Notary Public, or in extreme cases, submitted through official channels including your legal representation or counsel.  We also reserve the right to consider alternate forms of identification should you be unable to comply with the above standards. Finally, we reserve the right to refuse to act on your request if we have exhausted all reasonable means of verifying your identity and remain unable to verify that you are who you claim to be.

Additionally, if you are requesting the personal data of somebody else or are requesting that we act upon certain GDPR rights of somebody else, you are required to submit proof of your own identity and proof of your legal authority to make requests on behalf of the data subject (the individual whose data we possess), including one of the following items:

  * Written consent signed by the data subject (in certain circumstances at our discretion, we reserve the right to require this letter to be notarized)
  * A certified Power of Attorney document
  * Proof that you have parental rights over the data subject if they are legally considered a child

If any part of your request is unclear or requires further clarification of any sort, we will contact you before processing your request. If we are unable to process your request for any reason, we will contact you with an explanation. If the data you request would compromise the personal data or rights of another individual or individuals, we will first contact the applicable parties to secure permission to include their data in your request. We will also contact you if another individual’s request would compromise your own personal data or personal rights.

Certain laws may allow or require us to deny processing of your information or provision of your personal information. Additionally, if we have destroyed or have made your personal data anonymous (as GDPR allows) as part of our data security and integrity practices, we will be unable to provide it to you. In this case, your personally identifiable data either no longer exists or can no longer be used to identify you both in our internal and external systems.

**Mail Preferences**

Email: Biblica communicates with our customers through email. An “unsubscribe” link is provided on every email we send. If you are receiving email from us and wish to stop receiving communication via email, simply click on the “unsubscribe” link provided and you will immediately and automatically cease receiving email promotions from us. If you have any issues with the unsubscribe link, you may request removal via our [Contact Us form](https://www.biblica.com/about/contact-us/).

Sharing mailing lists with third parties: Biblica may enter into alliances, partnerships, or other arrangements with third parties who may be given access to contact information including your name and address, for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think may be of interest to you. Donor information is not shared in these arrangements. If you would prefer to not receive mailings from these organizations, please let us know by contacting us toll-free at 800-497-1121 or _contacting us here_.

Donor information (such as name, address, e-mail address) that you entrust to Biblica is not shared with any third party without your permission to do so.

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on our web site may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer SSL, 128 bit encryption services. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP. Please _contact us here_ , or call 1-800-524-1588, if you have any questions or concerns.

**How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?**

You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by contacting us at the above contact information.

Your California Privacy Rights. Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents who have an established relationship with us are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates’ direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following page: _Contact Us_. You can also mail the request to: Biblica, 1820 Jet Stream Drive, Colorado Springs, CO 80921. Please allow 30 days for a response.

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by web sites linked to or from our web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our web site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our web site to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites which have a link on our web site, is subject to that web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Your Consent**

By visiting and using our web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. At any time you may request to view any and all changes and updates, via surface mail.

If you are a citizen residing within the European Union, you have the right to withdraw consent at any time by following the procedures outlined above under the GDPR section. Upon withdrawal of your consent, you agree to immediately cease all use of our website and digital platforms. If you choose to continue use of our website or digital platforms after withdrawing consent, you understand that our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy will again apply to you (depending on your location and jurisdiction you reside under, this may not require your manual consent) and we may begin collecting personal information about you and your browsing behavior once again as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Notification of Changes**

The Privacy Policy is subject to periodic review and change. In order to view the current Privacy Policy, simply check this section of the website. If we materially change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate, so users are aware of what information we collect, how it is used, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. In some cases when we post a notice, we may also email users who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

**How Do We Communicate With You**

If we need, or are required, to contact you concerning any event that involves information about you, we may do so by email, telephone, or mail.

**Most Recent Privacy Policy**

This document, last updated on 6/04/2018 is our most recent and only active privacy policy. It supersedes all prior privacy policies we previously have had in place and your continued use of this website and service is contingent on your acceptance of this privacy policy in whole, or as much as in legally applicable.

Biblica has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices. The bottom line:

**Personal information (such as name, address, e-mail address) that you entrust to Biblica will never be shared with any third party without your permission to do so.**

##### Collection of Information

Biblica does not collect personal information without your knowledge while you are visiting our web site. However, Biblica allows you to provide personal information on our web site. The type of information we collect directly corresponds with the service you request. For instance, you can offer your thoughts, opinions, prayers, concerns, ideas, personal experiences, questions and/or suggestions to our articles or materials, or you can request that a resource be sent to you directly. The type of information we collect is only the information necessary to facilitate our response to your specific request such as your name and contact information. If you request to have a resource sent to you, Biblica will collect the information necessary to complete this transaction that may include your contact information, credit card number, and other transaction information. If you offer your thoughts, comments, opinions, concerns, ideas, personal experience testimonies, request prayer, ask questions, etc., Biblica collects that information and may use the information in one of the ways set forth in the following section titled “Use of Information.”

##### Use of Information

Biblica retains all rights to use the information provided by you to:

  * Respond to your correspondence, questions, comments, suggestions, thoughts, opinions, prayers, concerns, or ideas to fulfill a resource request.
  * Process your request for resources from our online Scripture catalog or donation service.
  * Continually update, develop, design, and customize the content of our web site to meet the needs, interests, and requests of our audience.
  * Publish your comments or testimonials in our marketing material.
  * Contact you via e-mail to confirm specific resource or information requests, inform you of new products and special offers, or provide information we think may be of particular interest to you.

##### E-Mail Lists

Subscription to an e-mail list provided on Biblica.com requires permission of the e-mail address owner. This is done through a double opt-in process and is recorded to verify that the subscription is valid and complies with anti-spam regulations. We not solicit or use rented lists to acquire subscriptions. E-mail lists include contact information such as our postal address, phone, list manager e-mail address, and immediate unsubscribe button. We do not share your e-mail address with anyone or subscribe your email address to other Biblica lists.

##### Copyright ©

All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, images, audio/video clips and streams, and software is the property of Biblica, a Colorado nonprofit corporation, or its content suppliers, all of which is protected by the copyright laws of the United States and worldwide by various copyright and intellectual property laws and treaties. Any use, including reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display or performance of content on this site, is strictly prohibited without the express written consent of Biblica unless otherwise expressly stated herein. See also [Terms of Use](https://www.biblica.com/en-us/about-us/terms-of-use/).

##### Trademarks ™

New International Version and NIV® (collectively, “NIV”) are registered trademarks of Biblica in the United States and other countries. Other trademarks of Biblica may be added from time to time on this site as well. In order to preclude confusion among our visitors, the trademarks and service marks of Biblica may not be used in any manner in connection with any product or service that is not a product or service of Biblica.

New International Reader’s Version and NIrV® (collectively, “NIrV”) are registered trademarks of Biblica in the United States and other countries. Other trademarks of Biblica may be added from time to time on this site as well. In order to preclude confusion among our visitors, the trademarks and service marks of Biblica may not be used in any manner in connection with any product or service that is not a product or service of Biblica.

##### Disclaimer

THIS SITE IS PROVIDED BY BIBLICA ON AN “AS IS” BASIS, AND BIBLICA MAKES NO REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THE SITE OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, OR PRODUCTS INCLUDED ON THIS SITE. TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY APPLICABLE LAW, BIBLICA DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. BIBLICA WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS SITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES.

##### Applicable Law

This site is created and controlled by Biblica in the State of Colorado, United States of America. The laws of the State of Colorado will govern these disclaimers, terms, conditions and notices, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of laws. Biblica reserves the right to make changes to this site, and to any of the disclaimers, terms, conditions, and notices contained in this site, at any time.

##### Links

This site contains links to other sites. Biblica is not responsible for either the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

##### Security of My Giving Account

Your information integrity is of utmost importance to us. The service we use for receiving online donations, Authorize.net, is PCI Compliant, and is dedicated to providing excellent service for our online donors. PCI Compliance is the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard, a world-wide benchmark mandated by the card associations for the protection of cardholder identity and transaction information.

##### Correct/Update

To change or modify information previously provided, simply call us at 1-800-987-3595.

##### Terms of Use

  * See also Terms of Use
